Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Information Files, c. 1900-present UA.Info.Files
ULS Archives & Special Collections
University of Pittsburgh Archives Information Files
c. 1900-present
ULS Archives & Special Collections
University of Pittsburgh. Archives Service Center
UA.Info.Files
40 Linear Feet
The University of Pittsburgh Archives Information Files contain brochures, news clippings, press releases and other materials about University of Pittsburgh offices and departments, as well as some programs and events. There is at least one folder in the Information File for each of the headings listed below. Items in the UA Information Files are available for public use in the Archives Service Center Reading Room and may be photocopied upon request.
Acquisition Information
Created by various University Archivists since 1968.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Faculty papers; University of Pittsburgh; Women; Societies; Social action; Architecture; Associations; Business and Industry; Churches and Synagogues; Education; Environment; Ethnic groups; Government; Health and medicine; Labor; Politics
- A
  - Academic Computing; SEE Provost
  - Academic Integrity
  - Activities Fair; SEE Student Activities
  - Activities Handbook
  - Addison H. Gibson Laboratory; SEE Schools- Medicine
  - Addresses
  - Administration, Vice President for
  - Administrative Officers
  - Administrative Services; SEE Business Affairs
  - Admissions
  - Advising Center
  - Advisory Council on Regional Development
  - Affirmative Action Program (Equal Opportunity)
  - AIDS
  - Air Force ROTC
  - Air Glow Observatory; SEE Space Research Coordination Center
  - Alcohol
  - Allegheny Observatory
  - Allen Magee Scaife Hall of the Health Sciences Professions; SEE Schools- Health Professions
  - Alliance College Polish Collection
  - Alliance Francaise
  - Alma Mater
  - Alternative Curriculum
  - Alumni Association
  - Alumni Association, African-American
  - Alumni- Biography
  - Alumni Hall
  - Alumni Office; SEE Development and Alumni Affairs
  - Alzheimer Disease Research Center ARDC
  - American Council on Education College Study in Intergroup Relations; SEE Intergroup Relations
  - American Experience; SEE Special Seminars, Office of
  - Annual Giving Fund; SEE ALSO Development and Alumni Affairs
  - Apartments; SEE Housing
  - Applied Science and Technology, Center for; SEE Foundation for Applied Science and Technology
  - Archives of Industrial Society
  - Archives Service Center
  - Arms Control; SEE Center for Arms Control & International Security Studies
  - Arsenal Family and Children's Center
  - Art Exhibitions
  - Arts Information International
  - Artworks, Hillman, Assorted University Art and Chancellors Residence
  - Asian Studies Programs; SEE ALSO University Center for International Studies; SEE ALSO East Asian Language and Area Center
  - Assemblies; SEE ALSO Religious Activities
  - Assemblies- General
  - Assemblies- Memorial Services
  - Assemblies- Scholars' Day; SEE RG 0/10/71; SEE Convocations- Fall Honors Convocation
  - Assemblies- Student Union
  - Assemblies- Tap Day Exercises; SEE RG 0/10/7 (Discontinued as of 1971 according to Pitt News 3/25/71)
  - Association of American Universities (AAU)
  - Association of University Librarians (AUL)
  - Athletes, Famous; SEE ALSO University Archives Personal Files
  - Athletics- Baseball
  - Athletics- Basketball
  - Athletics- Bowling
  - Athletics- Cheerleading
  - Athletics- Football
  - Athletics- General
  - Athletics- Gymnastics
  - Athletics- Hockey
  - Athletics- Rifle Team
  - Athletics- Road Racing
  - Athletics- Soccer
  - Athletics- Swimming
  - Athletics- Tennis
  - Athletics- Track and Field
  - Athletics- Volleyball
  - Athletics- Women's Athletics
  - Athletics- Wrestling
  - Awards (includes Certificates)
- B
  - Babcock Room
  - Baccalaureate Education; SEE Curriculum Reform
  - Band
  - Benedum, Michael L., Hall of Engineering
  - Bellefield Annex
  - Ben Franklin Partnership Program; SEE Western Pennsylvania Advanced Technology Center
  - Biotechnology Center; SEE ALSO Strategy 21
  - Black Action Society
  - Black Community
  - Blacks
  - Blood Bank; SEE Central Blood Bank
  - Blood Drive
  - Blue and Gold Society
  - Board of Trustees/ Board of Trustees Biography
  - Book Center (University of Pittsburgh); SEE Book Stores
  - Book of Scholars; SEE Assemblies- Scholars' Day; SEE Convocations- Fall Honors Convocation
  - Book Stores
  - Bouquet Gardens
  - Bradford Campus
  - Brackenridge House; SEE Housing
  - Brashear, John A.; SEE Chancellor- Brashear, John A.
  - Braun Room
  - Bruce Hall
  - Bruce, Robert; SEE Chancellor- Bruce, Robert
  - Buckley Amendment
  - Budget; SEE Finance; SEE State-Pitt Relationship
  - Buhl Library; SEE Schools- Social Work & Library
  - Buildings; SEE [Building name]
  - Business Affairs (Business and Finance)
  - By-Laws of the University
- C
  - Calendar
  - Campus-Based Information System
  - Campus Bus and Shuttle
  - Campus Laboratory School; SEE Falk School
  - Campus, Maps of (descriptive maps only); SEE ALSO flat files
  - Campus Nursery and Child Development Center
  - Campus of the Future; SEE ALSO Telecommunications
  - Cardiac Work Evaluation Clinic (Falk Clinic); SEE University Health Center
  - Career Seminars
  - Careers; SEE University Counseling and Student Development Center
  - Cathedral of Learning
  - Censorship
  - Center for American Music
  - Center for Arms Control & International Security Studies (established 1975)
  - Center for Biotechnology and Bioengineering; SEE Biotechnology Center; SEE Strategy 21
  - Center for Instructional Resources; SEE Communications Center (original name)
  - Center for International Biomedical Research
  - Center for Instructional Development and Distance Education
  - Center for International Security Studies; SEE Ridgway (Matthew B.) Center for International Security Studies
  - Center for Latin American Studies
  - Center for Medical Ethics
  - Center for Philosophy of Science
  - Center for Public and Community Service
  - Center for Regional Economic Studies
  - Center for Russian and East European Studies
  - Center for the Improvement of Teaching
  - Center of Environmental Epidemiology
  - Central Blood Bank
  - Central Business Services
  - Central Printing Department; SEE ALSO Business Affairs
  - Certificates from Certificate Programs
  - Chancellor- Bowman, John Gabbert
  - Chancellor- Brashear, John A.
  - Chancellor- Crawford, Stanton C.
  - Chancellor- Goff, Milton
  - Chancellor- Holland, W. J.
  - Chancellor- Kurtzman, David H.
  - Chancellor- McCormick, Samuel Black
  - Chancellor- McCracken, H. M.
  - Chancellor- McLaren, John Finlay
  - Chancellor- Morgan, Gilbert
  - Chancellor- Nordenberg, Mark A.
  - Chancellor- O'Connor, J. Dennis
  - Chancellor- Posvar, Wesley
  - Chancellor- Woods, George
  - Chancellors (Past)
  - Chancellor's Search for Committee
  - Chancellor's Residence
  - Chaplains Association; SEE University Chaplains
  - Charters (replaced by Restated Articles of Incorporation)
  - Chautauqua; SEE Summer Sessions
  - Chautauqua at Pitt
  - Cheating
  - Cheers (University of Pittsburgh); SEE RG 90/8/26/1
  - Chemistry Building; SEE Chevron Science Center (for information after November 1987)
  - Chevron Science Center; SEE Chemistry Building (for information before November 1987)
  - Child Development, Office of
  - Child Guidance Center
  - Child Service Demonstration Center
  - Children's Hospital
  - China-Pitt Exchange
  - Chinese Language and Area Center
  - Citizenship Information Center
  - City Theatre Company
  - Civil Defense
  - Clapp Hall
  - Class Schedules; SEE Downtown Division; SEE Schools- Medicine
  - Classrooms; SEE Physical Plant
  - Cleft Palate Research Center
  - Clinical Research Unit; SEE University Health Center
  - Coal Research
  - Coffee House
  - College Association
  - College Study of Intergroup Relations; SEE Intergroup Relations
  - College Themes; SEE Schools- Arts and Sciences- Department of English
  - Commencement
  - Committee on Advanced Industrial Societies
  - Commonwealth Fund Research Project; SEE Schools- Medicine
  - Commonwealth Relations
  - Communication Center; SEE University Center for Instructional Resources
  - Community and Urban Services; SEE Urban and Community Services, Office of
  - Community Development Institute
  - Community Series; SEE Schools- College of General Studies; SEE Schools- College of General Studies- Informal Courses, Lectures & Programs (1964-1973)
  - Commuters
  - Comparative Literature Program
  - Comptroller's Office (1960-1986)
  - Comptroller's Office (1987-present)
  - Computers
  - Computing and Information Service; SEE Computing Services & Systems Development (after August 1989)
  - Computing Services & Systems Development
  - Concerts
  - Conferences (Pitt-related); SEE ALSO conferences sponsored by and filed under various schools, including Schools- Medicine, Schools- Social Work, etc.
  - Conference Coordination, Office of
  - Conflict of Interest
  - Congratulatory Documents to the University; SEE oversize cabinet
  - Continued Education; SEE ALSO Schools- Graduate
  - Convocations- Fall Honors Convocation (before 1958); SEE Assemblies- Scholars' Day
  - Coordinated Education Center
  - Core Curriculum
  - Cornerstones
  - Coronation of the Senior Queen; SEE RG 55/4/1
  - Cost (Charles L.) Sports Center
  - Council; SEE University Senate
  - Council for European Studies
  - Counseling Center; SEE University Counseling and Student Development Center
  - Course Evaluation
  - Courses
  - Crawford, Stanton C.; SEE Chancellor- Crawford, Stanton C.
  - Crawford Hall
  - Credit Union
  - Crime Alerts/ Crime Notices
  - Croghan-Schenley Room
  - Cultural and Educational Exchange Program; SEE ALSO Pitt Abroad; Foreign Students; International Studies Program; University Center for International Studies; International Exchange Program
  - Curriculum; SEE Academic Integrity
  - Curriculum Reform
- D
  - Dances: Concerts; Freshman Dance; Junior Prom; Military Ball; Senior Ball; Sophomore Hop
  - David Lawrence Hall
  - Dean of Students
  - Debating
  - Degrees; SEE Registrar
  - Desegregation and Conflict Center
  - DeSoto Hall
  - Development; SEE Planning
  - Development and Alumni Affairs; SEE ALSO Annual Giving Fund
  - Development and Alumni Affairs Travel Brochures (1969-1984)
  - Dickson Prize; SEE ALSO Schools- Medicine
  - Dinners and Luncheons
  - Discrimination; SEE ALSO Affirmative Action Program
  - Display Material
  - Diversity Task Force
  - Diversity Working Group
  - Dormitories and Residence Life, Office of; Resident Student Association; SEE Housing
  - Downtown Division: Banquets; Class Schedule; Dance Program
  - Drue Heinz Literature Prize
  - Drug Awareness Program
  - D. T. Watson School of Physiatrics; SEE Watson School of Physiatrics
- E
  - East Asian Languages and Area Center
  - Eberly Hall
  - Educational Placement Office; SEE Schools- Education
  - Educational Research; SEE Office for Educational Research
  - EDUCOM
  - Elections Ballots
  - Emergencies; SEE Public Safety, Department of
  - Emergency Medicine Center
  - Employment; SEE Student Employment
  - Energy; SEE ALSO Energy and Environment Center; SEE Schools- Engineering
  - Energy and Environment Center
  - English Language Institute
  - Enterprise Corporation of Pittsburgh; SEE Western Pennsylvania Advanced Technology Center
  - Environment (Focus On)
  - Enrollment
  - Equal Employment; SEE Affirmative Action Program
  - Equal Opportunity Office; SEE Affirmative Action Program
  - Erie Center
  - Ethnic Studies
  - Executive Committee; SEE University Senate
  - Executive Secretary; SEE Administrative Officers
  - Eye and Ear Hospital
- F
  - Facilities Management
  - Facilities Management- Environmental Health and Safety
  - Faculty; SEE ALSO Mellon Professors; Personnel; Provost
  - Faculty and Staff Assistance Program
  - Faculty Club (changed to Pitt Club in 1993)
  - Faculty Development, Office of
  - Faculty Evaluation; SEE Course Evaluation
  - Faculty for Social Responsibility
  - Faculty, Graduate
  - Faculty Handbook; SEE ALSO LD6001.8 A221
  - Faculty News; SEE Pitt Publications
  - Faculty Orientation
  - Faculty Productivity
  - Faculty Salaries (includes clippings from 1950s)
  - Faculty/Staff Wellness Program
  - Falk School
  - Fall Convocation; SEE Convocations- Fall Honors Convocation
  - Far Eastern Studies; SEE Interdepartmental Majors
  - Fellowships; SEE Scholarships
  - Film Studies
  - Films
  - Finance
  - Financial Crisis- Litchfield Area
  - Financial Crisis- 1963-1969
  - Financial Crisis- 1969-1977
  - Fitch (William K.) Faculty Center
  - Focus on the Future (Career Planning Programs); SEE Assemblies- Student Union
  - Food Services
  - Football; SEE Athletics- Football
  - Forbes Quadrangle
  - Ford Foundation Report
  - Foreign Language Requirement; SEE Curriculum Reform
  - Foreign Policy Association; SEE Foreign Students
  - Foreign Students; SEE ALSO Cultural and Educational Exchange Program
  - Forensic and Musical League; SEE Pennsylvania Forensic and Musical League
  - Foundation for Applied Science and Technology
  - Foundations
  - Founder's Day
  - Fraternities
  - Fraternities- Buildings (near stadium)
  - Freshman Convocation
  - Freshmen Applications and Information (Pitt Preview); SEE ALSO High School Relations
  - Freshmen Events
  - Freshmen Handbooks; SEE Freshmen- Applications and Information
  - Frick (Henry Clay) Fine Arts Building (Henry Clay Frick Fine Arts Library); SEE University Library System
  - Frick School
  - Fringe Benefits; SEE Personnel
  - Fund Raising
- G
  - Gay Students at Pitt
  - General Assistance Center on School Desegregation and Conflict; SEE Desegregation and Conflict Center
  - General History File
  - Generations Together
  - Geography Newsletter; SEE Schools- Arts and Sciences- Department of Geography
  - Geology and Planetary Sciences
  - Geriatric Education Center of Pennsylvania
  - Gifts and Grants; SEE Treasurer
  - Gimbel's Pennsylvania Art Collection
  - Glee Club; SEE Musical Clubs
  - Goff, Milton; SEE Chancellor- Goff, Milton
  - Golden Panthers
  - Governmental Relations (includes new office established August 1975, the Office of Commonwealth Services)
  - Governor's School for International Studies
  - Grading Policy
  - Graduate Center for Public Works, Engineering, and Administration; SEE ALSO Schools- Graduate School of Public and International Affairs
  - Graduate Faculty; SEE Faculty, Graduate
  - Graduate Professional Student Association (GPSA)
  - Graduate Programs
  - Graduate Students; SEE Students, Graduate
  - Graduate Work in Industry; SEE Schools- Graduate School
  - Grants
  - Greek Week; SEE Fraternities
- H
  - Hand-In-Hand Festival
  - Handicapped
  - Harmarville Research Center; SEE University of Pittsburgh Applied Research Center (U-PARC)
  - Hazardous Materials Research Center
  - Health, Physical and Recreation Education; SEE Schools- Education- Department of Health, Physical and Recreational Education
  - Health and Safety Office
  - Health Benefits
  - Health Law Center; SEE ALSO Schools- Graduate School of Public Health
  - Health Policy Institute
  - Health Sciences Library System
  - Health Sciences, Office of
  - Heinz Chapel Choir
  - Heinz House
  - Heinz Lecture (Distinguished)
  - Heinz (Drue) Literature Prize; SEE Drue Heinz Literature Prize
  - Heinz Memorial Chapel; SEE ALSO Heinz Chapel Choir
  - Heinz Memorial Chapel, Chapel Services, Programs
  - Henry Clay Frick Fine Arts Department; SEE Schools- Fine Arts and Sciences- Department of Fine Arts
  - High School Media Clinic (Annual)
  - High School Relations
  - Higher Education Assistance Authority
  - Hill Education Project
  - Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania
  - History of the University- Promotional Materials, Small Statistical Publications
  - Holidays; SEE Calendar
  - Holland, W. J.; SEE Chancellor- Holland, W. J.
  - Homecoming Events; SEE ALSO Alumni Association
  - Honors Convocations, 1961-1962
  - Honorary Degrees; SEE RG 0/10/2/1-A for degrees 1849-1985; contact Chancellor's Office for current list
  - Honors Program; SEE ALSO University Honors College (1987)
  - Housing
  - Human Energy Research Laboratory
  - Human Resources, Office of Assistant Vice Chancellor; SEE ALSO Personnel
  - Human Research Subjects; SEE Institutional Review Boards
  - Hybridoma Center
- I
  - Identification Cards
  - Immigration Reform Act of 1986 (Regarding Staff Employment)
  - Inauguration of Chancellors; SEE (Name of individual chancellor); Chancellors (Past)
  - Inauguration Programs (from other schools)
  - Incorporators of the Original Pittsburgh Academy
  - Information Service (News and Publications)
  - Information Service (Pitt in the News)
  - Information Technology Steering Committee (Provost)
  - Information Utilization Laboratory
  - Institute for Higher Education; SEE Schools- Education
  - Institute for Local Government
  - Institute for Small Manufacturers
  - Institute for Urban Policy and Administration (previous to 1969: Institute of Local Government); SEE RG 90/30/7
  - Institute of Politics
  - Institute of Training and Organizational Development (1981); SEE Graduate School of Public and International Affairs for prior years
  - Institutes; SEE Conferences
  - Institutional Advancement
  - Institutional Development for Latin America
  - Institutional Research, Office of
  - Institutional Review Boards
  - Insurance
  - Integrated Student Information System (ISIS)
  - Intercultural House (started 1/6/1970)
  - Interdepartmental Majors
  - Interdisciplinary Programs
  - Intergroup Relations
  - International Committee Against Racism, Pitt Student Chapter
  - International Exchange Program; SEE Cultural and Educational Exchange Program; China-Pitt Exchange
  - International Intercollegiate Cosmopolitan Club
  - International Student Services Office (part of Student Affairs)
  - International Studies Association
  - International Studies Program (absorbed in 1968 by University Center for International Studies); SEE ALSO Cultural and Educational Exchange Program
  - Interscholastic Contests
  - Interuniversity Communications Council; SEE EDUCOM
  - Invitations (Miscellaneous)
  - Invitations (Miscellaneous), 1991-1997
  - Invitations (Miscellaneous), 1998-present
- J
  - Jazz (Jazz Hall of Fame, International Academy of)
  - Jewish History Project
  - Johnstown
  - Johnstown Center; SEE Regional Campuses- Johnstown
  - Joint Degree Program
- K
  - Kennedy (John Fitzgerald) Memorial Service; SEE Heinz Memorial Chapel
  - Khrushchev Visit
  - Knowledge Availability Systems Center
  - Kuntu Repertory Theatre; SEE Schools- Arts and Sciences- Black Studies Department
  - Kurtzman, David H.; SEE Chancellor- Kurtzman, David H.
- L
  - Lafayette Medal (Memorabilia)
  - Langley Hall
  - Lantern Night; SEE ALSO Alumnae Association RG 6/4/1; Alumni Association
  - Latin America
  - Latin American Projects; SEE Institutional Development for Latin America
  - Latin American Region; SEE Interdepartmental Majors
  - Latin American Studies; SEE Center for Latin American Studies
  - Learning Skill Center
  - Learning Research and Development Center (LRDC)
  - Lectures
  - Legal Awareness Committee
  - Legal Counsel Office
  - Lesbian and Gay Academic Association at Pitt
  - Liberal Club
  - Lilly, Josiah Kirby, Gift of the Foster Hall Collection; SEE Stephen Foster Memorial
  - Linguistic Program; SEE Schools- Arts and Sciences- Department of Linguistics, General
  - Litigation
  - Logo (University); SEE Seal, University; Litigation
  - Lothrop Hall
  - Loyalty Oath
  - Lutheran University Center
- M
  - McCormick, Samuel Black; SEE Chancellor- McCormick, Samuel Black
  - McCracken, H. M.; SEE Chancellor- McCracken, H. M.
  - McKay Fund (Department of Economics)
  - McLaren, John Finlay; SEE Chancellor- McLaren, John Finlay
  - Magee Women's Hospital
  - Mail
  - Management and Budget, Vice President; SEE ALSO Business and Finance
  - Management Information and Policy Analysis, Office of
  - Management Research Center
  - Management Research Center, MRC Briefs
  - Management Research Center, Reprint Series
  - Management Research Center, Technical Report
  - Management Research Center Annual Report to the Ford Foundation
  - Management Services (under Business and Finance Vice Chancellor)
  - Maps; SEE Campus, Maps of
  - Marshall Scholars
  - Maurice and Laura Falk Library of the Health Professions; SEE University Library System
  - Masonic Temple
  - Meadowcroft Shelter; SEE Schools- Arts and Sciences- Department of Anthropology
  - Measurement and Evaluation of Teaching
  - Measurement and Evaluation, Office of; SEE RG 15/14/2
  - Medical and Health Care Division (MHCD); SEE RG 90/44
  - Medical Center
  - Medical Research
  - Medieval and Renaissance Studies Center
  - Mellon Institute
  - Mellon Lecture; SEE Lectures
  - Mellon Professors; SEE ALSO Faculty
  - Men's Council
  - Men's Dormitory Council
  - Mervis Hall
  - Metropolitan Science Technology Library
  - Mid-Atlantic Technology Applications Center; SEE ALSO NASA Industrial Application Center (NIAC) before 1/1/1992
  - Midday Series Programs
  - Middle States Evaluation; SEE RG 0/0/1
  - Military Department; SEE ALSO R.O.T.C.
  - Miss Maggie's Newsletter
  - Model Cities Program (Pitt Participation 1970)
  - Montefiore Hospital
  - Morgan, Gilbert; SEE Chancellor- Morgan, Gilbert
  - Mortar Board (Senior Women's Honor Society); SEE Women
  - Motorcycle Club
  - Mulert Memorial Room
  - Music- Songs of the University of Pittsburgh; SEE RG 38
  - Musical Clubs; SEE RG 38; Band; Glee Club
- N
  - Nanoscience and Engineering, Institute of
  - NASA Industrial Application Center (NIAC); SEE ALSO Mid-Atlantic Technology Applications Center (after 1/1/1992)
  - National Center for Juvenile Justice (1309 C.L.)
  - National Forensic League; SEE Debating
  - National Teacher Corps
  - Nationality Rooms- African Heritage
  - Nationality Rooms- Armenian
  - Nationality Rooms- Austrian
  - Nationality Rooms- Chinese
  - Nationality Rooms- Czechoslovakia
  - Nationality Rooms- Dedications
  - Nationality Rooms- Early American
  - Nationality Rooms- English
  - Nationality Rooms- Finnish
  - Nationality Rooms- French
  - Nationality Rooms- General
  - Nationality Rooms- German
  - Nationality Rooms- Greek
  - Nationality Rooms- Hungarian
  - Nationality Rooms- Indian
  - Nationality Rooms- Irish
  - Nationality Rooms- Israeli
  - Nationality Rooms- Italian
  - Nationality Rooms- Korean, 2015
  - Nationality Rooms- Lithuanian
  - Nationality Rooms- Norwegian
  - Nationality Rooms- Pennsylvania German
  - Nationality Rooms- Polish
  - Nationality Rooms- Philippine, 2019
  - Nationality Rooms- Romanian
  - Nationality Rooms- Russian
  - Nationality Rooms- Scottish
  - Nationality Rooms- Swedish
  - Nationality Rooms- Swiss, 2012
  - Nationality Rooms- Syria Lebanon
  - Nationality Rooms- Ukrainian
  - Nationality Rooms- Yugoslavia
  - N.E.E.D.; SEE Negro Educational Emergency Drive
  - Negro Educational Emergency Drive (N.E.E.D.)
  - Networked Information Services Group
  - Neuroscience Center
  - New Careers Educational Program
  - New Professional Association
  - News and Publications Office; SEE Information Service (News and Publications)
  - NMR Institute (Nuclear Magnetic Resonance)
  - Nobel Prizes
  - Nordenberg, Mark A.; SEE Chancellor- Nordenberg, Mark A.
  - Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Institute; SEE NMR Institute
  - Nurses Residence; SEE RG 13/42/7
  - Nutrition Center
  - Nutrition Clinic; SEE University Health Center
  - N.Y.A. (National Youth Adminsitration)
- O
  - Oakland
  - Oakland Corporation
  - Oakland Library Consortium
  - Oceanographic Station
  - O'Connor, J. Dennis; SEE Chancellor- O'Connor, J. Dennis